<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!--  PPA - 1 / Assignment 2 - World of Zuul
      Gabriele Trotta (K21006956)  -->
<!-- 
    This xml file is part of the project called "IUNI".
    It's a simple text adventure game, where you can walk around 
    and interact with characters and items, in order to regain your memory.

    This file contains all the information regarding the different endings of the game.

    Each <end> node has one attribute:
        * "id" : the identifier for the specific ending
    Each of these nodes can have two types of children : <text> and <pie>.
    The <text> contains the content of the parent ending. You should specify the ending,
    with the ending's outcome and the name and you should write a capitalized "ENDING".

    The <pie> contains the text of the parent ending, given the player has a pie-slice item.

    author : Gabriele Trotta (K21006956)

-->
<allEnds>
    <end id="good">
        <text>
            You see a familiar figure standing 5m away from you talking with some sort of receptionist.
            Near her, you see a little child, holding her hand really tightly.
            You decide to come closer to them.

            Receptionist : 
                We don't know if he still remembers any of his youth, and if he might've forgotten
                even most of his adult life. We might need to move him to a more specialised faculty.
            
            Rebecca (woman standing) :
                But I am sure that he still remembers us! He can't have forgotten all the times he spent with
                Noah! I am sure that if we-
            
            Charlie (Player) :
                *takes off hat*
                Hi Rebecca, I would like to stand with you on that one.
            
            Noah, the little kid, proceeds to run up to our protagonist and hug him tightly.
            <pie>
                You remember you have a slice of a cherry pie, so you give it to your nephew;
                which is incidentally his favourite flavour.

                With tears in his eyes, and snot running from his nose, he thanks you with a beaming smile.
            </pie>

            GOOD ENDING : MEMORY RECOVERED AND FAMILY REUNITED
        </text>
    </end>

    <end id="bad1">
        <text>
            You find yourself lost in a dark room.
            You're scared and don't even know how to go back to the kitchen so you wander further ahead.
            The caretakers find you four hours later, cuddled up in a ball near a wall; in delusion.
            They decide that maybe you need more therapy, and put you under strict supervision.
            
            BAD ENDING : LOST AND AFRAID.
        </text>
    </end>

    <end id="bad2">
        <text>
            You foolishly decided to hand over a knife to a startled carer.
        </text>
        <pie>
            To sweeten the situation you try to give a slice of pie to the carer, but to no avail.
        </pie>
        <text>
            The carer, reasonably shocked, called psychologists and after a careful evauluation,
            they decided to put you in a specialised facility for a more grave psychological condition.
    
            BAD ENDING : ANOMALOUS DANGEROUS BEHAVIOUR
        </text>
    </end>

    <end id="secret">
        <text>
            You find yourself in a road with pedestrians walking, cars moving and dogs barking.
            You feel that you want to move away from the strange house you found yourself earlier, and
            have a long sustained walk. You get to a green park, where you sit on a bench and gently fall asleep.
        
            SECRET ENDING : CALM FUGITIVE
        </text>
    </end>
</allEnds>
